Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series XXXVII: Ideas A-F, 1986-1999
  - From Transforms of Problems to Option Process, Undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Barrier Options in Non-lognormal Processes, Undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Binary Calls, Undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Balter Binomial Model, Undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Cap Structure, 1997-12-18 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Shapiro/Titman, An Integrated Approach to Corporate Risk Management, Undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Titman, Sheridan; The Effect of Forward Markets on the Debt-Equity Mix of Investor Portfolios and the Optimal Capital Structure of Firms, JFQA March 1985, Undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Titman, Sheridan; The Effect of Capital Structure on a Firm's Liquidation Decision, JFE 1984, Undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Madan & Soubra, Design and Marketing of Financial Products, RFS 1991, Undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Titman, Sheridan; Interest Rate Swaps and Corporate Financing Choices, 1990-06 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - CEV Dynamics and Randomization, Undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - CAPM & Risk Neutral Pricing, Undated (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - CEV Barrier Option & Lecture Notes in Statistics by Hans Rudolf Lerche, 1986-1995 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - CIR & AMOL, 1990-12 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Concentrated Stock Risk, 1997-12-09 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Complex Analysis in Finance, 1998-10-30 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Convergence at Binomial Models, Undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Correlation, 1996-12-05-1997-07-28 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Credit Risk Paper, Undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Dividends, 1997-09-25-1997-09-26 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Dividend Protected Convertible, Undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Spatially Dependent or Discrete Dividends, Undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Dynamic Basket Options, 1997-11-07 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Options on Fixed Weight Portfolios, US Options on Fixed Share Portfolios, Undated (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Duality Between Volatility & Options, 1998-04-30 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Electricity Derivatives, Undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Entropy Maximization, 1996-12-19 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Exponential Polynomials, Undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Feynman-Kac, Undated (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - FIJI, 1996-11-1998-09-28 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Jarrow & Madan, Hedging Contingent Claims on Semimartingales, Undated (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Filtering Volatility, 1997-02-11 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Forward PDC's, Undated (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Future Valuation Theory, Undated (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Series XXXVIII: Ideas G-Q, 1989-1998
  - Fundamental Role of Duration of American Options, Untitled (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Fast Fourier Transform's (FFT's) in BS Model, 1997-08-08-1997-11-21 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Fourier Basis, 1997-11-06 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Probabilistic Interpretation of Fourier Inversion, Undated (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Financial Interpretation of Fourier Series, Undated (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Complex Probabilities, Undated (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Hedging, Undated (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Using HCC to Determine Boundary of Call, Undated (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Using HCC to Determine Boundary, Undated (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Duffie, Darrell; An Extension of the Black-Scholes Model of Security Valuation, Journal of Economic Theory 1988, Undated (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Fundamental Power Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Static Hedging with Drift, Undated (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Hedging Paper with Sheridan, 1996-03-16 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Hedging with the Wrong Volatility, Undated (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Hedging Asian Put with European Put, Undated (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Hedging Exotics with Vanillas, Undated (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Hedging Arbitrary Timing Risk, Undated (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Hedging Multivariate Options with Univariate Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Historical vs. Implieds, Undated (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Introduction to Probability Theory for Physicists, Undated (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Jumps & Correlation, 1997-01-22 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Jumps Forecaster & Trader, Undated (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Laplace Transform in Space, Undated (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Liquidity Reserves, Undated (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Long Term Desk Volatility, Undated (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Market Span, Undated (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Model Risk, 1997-11 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Monte Carlo of Randomization, Undated (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Monthly Newsletter, 1996-05-16-1996-10-21 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Neuro-Dynamic Programming, Undated (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - O'Connor Notes, 1989-10-05-1990-08-17 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - One Parameter Exponential Family, Undated (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Operators & Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Options on Merging Stocks, 1997-09-09 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Optimal Static Hedging, Undated (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Path-Dependent Options & Local Times, Undated (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Karatzas & Shreve, Trivariate Density of Brownian Motion, Its Local and Occupation Times, with Application to Stochastic Control; Annals of Probability 1984, Undated (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Path Dependent Arrow Debreu Securities, Undated (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Political Risk, Undated (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Portfolios of Derivatives, 1998-10-14 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Power Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Preferences Based Pricing for Real Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Pricing Corp. Securities Relative to Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Pricing as a Markov Central Problem, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Process Free Arbitrage, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Pseudo-European Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - Prop Trading, 1997-12-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Quadratic Richardson, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 119)
- Series XXXIX: Ideas R-Z, 1988-1998
  - Randomization & Transforms, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Random Time Stop Binomial Model, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Randomized Rebalancing, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Randomization & Trading when Delta moves by X, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rule of Convergence of Option Value to Payoff, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Regression Analysis of DOP, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Resettable Collar, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Resistance Levels, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rho Bucketing, 1997-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Richardson Extrapolation of Bushy Trees, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Risk as Quadratic Variation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Risk Neutral Valuation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ross, Stephen; Samuelson's Fallacy of Large Numbers Revisited, 1998-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - WLLN & RN Problems, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Siegel's Paradox, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - STARCH Model, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Settlement Delays, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Shew BM, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Static Hedge as a Central Variate, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Static Hedging of Final Income Derivs, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Static Hedging of Exotic Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Static Hedging of Int. Rate Options, 1997-07-31; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Björk, Di Masi, Kabanov, & Runggaldier; Towards a General Theory of Bond Markets, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Static Hedging & Jumps, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Stochastic Vol. - Misc., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Stock Loan Rebates, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Stopping Time at Occup Time, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Spanning with Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Student t Process, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Swaps, 1998-01-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Telegrapher's Equation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - TIBS, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Shimko, David C.; The Valuation of Multiple Claim Insurance Contracts, 1992-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Brown & Company, Deep Discounts for the Qualified Investor, 1990-11-30; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Tax Option, 1998-07-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Time Dependent CEV, 1988-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Time Wave Decomposition, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Trinomial Processes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Vol. Trading of MS, 1997-12-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Vol. Forecasting, 1995-1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Volatility Probes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Vol. Smile, 1994-1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Which Volatility to Hedge With?, Undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Series XL: Implied Correlation, 1997-2005
  - Implied Correlation, 2004-2005; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - COV Swap Revisited, 2004-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Implied Correlation of (-1, 1) as an Arbitrage Indicator, 2004-12-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Positive Definite Functions, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Local Vol. Models with 3 Currency Pairs, 2004-12-13; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Straddle Process & Distance Measures, 2004-12-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Stochastic Exponentials as Exchange Rates, 2005-01-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - FX IV Constraints, 2004-12-15 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Carr-Lee to [?] Options on the Cross?, 2004-12-15 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Asea & Ncube, Heterogenous Information Arrival and Option Pricing, 1997-03 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Bruno's FX A b Talk, 2005-01-24 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Series XLI: Implied Volatility, 1999-2005
  - Notes, 2004-11-17-2004-12-08 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - P&L from Delta Hedging a Call at its Running Implied Volatility, Undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - ATM d(subscript 1) = c, Undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - FVAs, 1999-07-28-2004-11-29 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Supported Stochastic IV Modelling, 2004-09-15-2004-11-26 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - MJD Delta Hedging, 2004-10-28 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - FX Options Delta - J, 2004-10-13 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Risk Neutral Drift of Various Selection of (ATM) Implied, 2004-12 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Effect of IV Skew Level on IV Skew Dynamics, 2004-11-04 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Delta Hedging of Running QV, 2004-11-02-2004-11-03 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Barone-Adesi, Engle & Mancini; GARCH Options in Incomplete Markets, 2004-10 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Static Hedging Rewrite, 2004-05-20-2004-09-02 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Carr & Wu, Static Hedging of Standard Options, 2004-05-19-2004-05-20 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Revision of Static Hedging of Standard Options, Version 14, 2002-11-26-2003-05-17 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Robust Representation of Var Swap Using Dynamic Trading in Underlying Factor at the Median Call, 2004-11-26-2004-12-13 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Sticky Strike, 2005-03-09 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - ATM FI > FVd Swap, 2004-12-06 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Replicating Vol. Swap, Trading in ATMF Straddle in Bachelier?, 2004-12-06 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Bachelier Results, 2004-12-01-2004-12-05 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - FVA & Market Models of IV, Undated (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Risk Reversals in Bachelier, 2004-12-06 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Skewness Swap, 2004-11-29-2004-12-08 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Comments Pg. 5-6, 2005-01 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Economic Relevance of Implied Volatility, 2002-12-12-2004-02-09 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Carr & Lee, Put Call Symmetry Revisited 2003, 2004-01-05 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Gatheral, Jim; Lecture 3: Jumps, Lecture 7: Replication of QV Based Payoffs, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Verma, Arun; Formulating Implied Volatility in Terms of Characteristic Function, 2003-12-15 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - FT Call and Implied Volatility, 2003-12-13-2003-12-16 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Approximating IV in Terms of Option Price, Undated (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Lee, Roger; Implied Volatility: Statistics, Dynamics, and Probabilistic Interpretation, 2002-11-22 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Local Volatility and Implied, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Matytsin, Andrew; Overheads, 1999-09-25-2000-01-29 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Gatheral, Jim; Modeling the Implied Volatility Surface, 2003-05-22 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Gatheral, Jim; Replication of Volatility Derivatives, 2003-12-09 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Weierstrass Transform & Implied Vol., 2003-07-13-2003-07-31 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Interpreting Implied, 2000-10-22-2001-11-07 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Stochastic IV as Stochastic Time Change, 2000-09-25-2001-08-06 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Economic Interpretation of Implied Vol., 2002-05-21 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Misc. IV, 2001-12-25 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Generalized Inverse Gaussian Distribution, 2005-12-16-2005-12-19 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Seshadri & Wesolowski, Mutual Characterizations of the Gamma and the Generalized Inverse Gaussian Laws by Constancy of Regression, circa 2001 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Types of Financial Calculation, O.C.I.A.M Presentation, Undated (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Implied Total Variance as the Inverse of Generalized Incomplete Gamma Function, 2005-06-15-2005-12-25 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Gaussian Inverse, Gaussian Formulation, 2005-12-14-2005-12-16 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Bachelier IV & Special Functions, 2005-12-09-2005-12-17 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Implied Volatility Approximation in Black with JTD, 2005-11-28 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Incomplete Gamma Function Inversion, 2005-12-10 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Inverse Gaussian / Wald Distribution Function Inverse / Percentage Points, 2005-12-16-2005-12-20 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - AMOL for Bachelier, 2005-12-02-2005-12-05 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - AMOL for Black IV, 2005-12-02 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Implied Volatility Restriction for FI, 2003-10-17-2004-03-23 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Econ Rel of IV Rewrite, 2004-02-09-2004-06-01 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Trading and Hedging Options, 2001-07 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Biv TSE of Black as an Improved Implied Volatility, 2002-10-22-2002-10-23 (Box 18, Folder 108)